I've had way too much to drink.
Idiot.
You're not supposed to kill any of the hostages, Chess.
Oh, crap.
Hey, human.
You can't die without my permission.
Okay?
I'm so sorry, Lord Crowley.
I got carried away.
Don't worry about it.
We've got plenty more where he came from.
Hear that, Horn?
You should have some, too, while he's still warm.
When are you going to learn to exhibit a little self-control?
You're a noble, not a savage.
Jeez.
Keep acting all uptight like that
and you'll miss out on all the good stuff.
Wouldn't you agree with me, Lord Crowley?
It wouldn't hurt for you to take life more seriously.
What?
Come on.
We need to discuss today's attacks.
It seems the humans finally found their backbones.
This Nagoya invasion of theirs was an act of war
and we must strike back.
Hmm.
You're right about that.
Hey, Chess.
Come here for a second, will you?
Huh?
Yeah, okay.
Uh, what did you do that for?
Well, I just wanted to see which weapon was stronger.
A human's blade or that of a vampire.
But, Lord Crowley, whichever weapon you hold is bound to be the strongest one, isn't it?
True, but that's not what I'm interested in.
Could you elaborate, my lord?
Hmm.
I'm afraid the humans are gaining too much power too quickly.
That's how they managed to take down so many nobles.
Just look at this weapon.
It's cursed, so it could kill any one of us.
However, this isn't the sort of thing they'd figure out on their own.
Someone must be leaking them information.
My lord, are you suggesting there might be a traitor among us working with the humans?
Yes, and a high-ranking one at that.
See?
Thanks to this curse, this wound isn't healing at all.
You girls need to be careful out there, okay?
I'll get you a bandage right away.
You can drink from it if you like.
Huh?
Ah!
But, Lord Crowley, I'm not worthy.
In that case, can I have a drink?
You already drained to that human, now you're just being greedy.
I'll accept your gracious offer.
No fair!
Why does she get to taste it?
Is there something wrong?
Hmm.
I was just wondering who the puppet master for this ambitious human operation might be.
Let's think.
Was it Queen Krul-Tepish or perhaps Ferret Bathory's doing?
Or maybe even...
Maybe who?
Never mind.
It can't be possible that a human's responsible for pulling the strings.
So, how long do we have to wait around here exactly?
The other squad should be joining us by 2.20.
Okay, but what if they don't show?
Then we have to assume that they're dead.
What's the time?
Already 2.13.
Is the lieutenant colonel here?
No, not yet.
I see.
Stand by for the time being.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, Shinua.
Hmm?
Weren't there 15 soldiers on that squad when we set out earlier?
There were.
They lost so many.
Aihara, did your team complete their mission?
We wouldn't be here if we hadn't.
You didn't lose any members of your squad.
I know.
I'm incredible.
Shut up.
Hey, Shinua.
Tell her what a great leader I am.
What?
Come on, why are you dragging me into this?
Um, I mean...
Hey, I'm glad you made it back alive.
We've got this area locked down.
You guys get some rest.
This is one of the newbies?
That's right.
Now, what was his name again?
Don't tell me you've forgotten already!
And after giving me so much crap about not remembering our target.
Just joking around.
He's Yuichiro, Hyakuya.
I see.
Thanks, Hyakuya.
We'll take you up on your offer and use this time to recover some of our strength.
Please keep your eyes open.
Sure.
We've got your backs.
I guess this war really does have casualties.
That's right.
Many comrades will die.
But that's a soldier's life.
Trust me.
I know all about it.
That's why we have to make each day count.
If our lives are short, we'll live them together.
What are you guys doing standing around out here like lost puppies?
So tell me, did you complete your mission?
Yeah, we killed our guy.
And what about your squad?
Piece of cake.
Yeah, right.
Narumi.
Yes, sir.
So how did our noobs fare today?
Did they drag you down too much?
Huh.
They managed to survive at least.
Actually, they did an outstanding job.
Really, each of them impressed me.
Huh.
What's that?
Say it again louder.
Don't get full of yourself.
That hurt.
AiHara, you lost eight of your men?
Um, they were killed, sir.
I apologize.
Lieutenant Colonel.
I failed my squad.
I knew there'd be losses.
Our comrades' deaths are on my hands, not yours.
No, sir.
I should have been a better leader.
Listen to me.
You saved six of your men.
Narumi, any word from the others?
Nothing, sir.
All right, then.
There's no time to stand around and wait.
We'll have to go ahead and start our next mission without them.
What are we gonna do now?
The soldiers assigned to kill the three nobles in City Hall
found themselves completely overwhelmed.
The vampires are holding 25 of them hostage.
Oh, no.
We're definitely gonna need those men for future missions.
Our new objective is to kill the three nobles and rescue our comrades.
Lieutenant Colonel, please let me go on this mission, too.
I would really like to be of assistance.
Not a chance.
I've got no room for someone who cries on the battlefield.
I'm kidding, okay?
Once we're done at City Hall, we'll rendezvous at the airport.
I need you to stay here and relay that information to the other squads that show up.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, sir!
Right.
Let's get moving, kids.
Yes, sir!
Got a second?
Let me guess.
You want to talk me out of this plan because it's likely a trap?
No, I get that we don't have a choice.
We need those squads to win this war.
It's not like there are many humans left to take their places.
Then what are you going to complain about?
Come on, Gurren.
I never said I had any complaints.
Many of our comrades were killed.
You don't always handle that well.
I was just worried about you, that's all.
This was a dangerous mission.
We were bound to lose some good soldiers.
But you're still going to beat yourself up about it.
That's part of your charm.
They're going to be fine.
Even those new troops are elites.
You don't need to worry about them.
You know, you're right.
I should believe in them.
I've got movement here.
You made it.
I was afraid you were dead.
We ran into a lot of trouble.
But we still managed to kill our assigned target.
That's great.
I'm so glad to see you.
Get out of here!
Meet the lieutenant colonel at the airport.
I can take care of this myself.
Damn you!
Hello, human.
You're going to answer some questions for me.
Everyone!
This is the code 284!
What's going on?
I was barely choking him.
The humans have poisoned themselves.
Now we can't torture them.
So you've got some kind of suicide pill in your mouth.
But I can't let you die yet.
I have a question I need to ask you.
Torture me all you want, bastard!
I'm not going to tell you a damn-
Keep quiet!
Pretend you're dead too.
You don't want the other vampires to find out you're alive.
I'll let you go if you answer my questions truthfully.
Got it?
Do you know a human named Yuichiro Hyakuya?
I can see from the look in your eyes that you do.
Tell me where he is if you want to live.
Kill me!
I won't tell out my comrade to-
Shut up!
You don't get to call yourself Yu's comrade!
Hold on.
Who are you?
Really?
Hey, Mika.
What are you doing over there?
Just checking on this human.
But she's dead too.
Why'd they go and kill themselves?
Are they stupid?
Hey!
Over here!
Hmm?
Find something.
Look at this.
Several vampires were killed here.
From the look of these clothes, I'd say Lukal Wesker's dead.
No way.
An entire army of humans wouldn't be able to kill a noble like him.
Lord Lachis!
Lord Rene!
Hmm?
The vampires underground have been wiped out!
What about Lord Mel Stefano?
We searched the tunnels, but we can't find him anywhere.
Seriously?
Something strange is going on here, and I don't like it.
Me neither.
Let's get moving.
Lord Crowley should be at City Hall.
He'll know what happened here.
Stop right there!
Make one move, and I'll slit your friend's throat!
Mika, I know you're kind of slow sometimes, but how did you miss that she was alive?
Capture her.
She'll prove useful.
I told you not to move!
Do you want this bloodsucker to die?
You can do whatever you want.
If he dies, it's his own fault.
Hold on.
I'll take care of this mess.
Shut your mouth!
All right.
So, Hiyakuya.
He left for City Hall not long ago.
If you and your friends go there too, everyone will be killed.
Why are you telling me this now?
Because you called him you.
I'm hoping that means you're a friend of his.
That's all the intelligence I have about Hiyakuya.
Do you understand what that means?
Die!
Not bad.
You had the rest of your men commit suicide, but here you are acting like a desperate fool trying to save your own life.
You want to live that badly?
I don't want to die!
Please don't kill me!
Then tell me where your comrades are.
Your squad is obviously too weak to be behind these attacks.
If I tell you, then you're not going to kill me, okay?
Right.
The Imperial Army's strongest soldiers are at this moment heading to the Botanical Garden in Higashiyama Park.
Their mission is to execute Zane Lindau.
Do you know him?
How do you not know who he is?
Lindau is the 17th progenitor.
So they know the name of a noble and where he's located.
This whole setup gives me a bad feeling.
What should we do?
We have to go and warn Lord Lindau.
Otherwise, we'll end up in big trouble.
Let's go.
That's super far away.
This is going to be such a pain.
Wait.
Please kill me.
Quickly.
I've no reason to live.
There's nothing left.
I'm not getting my hands dirty.
If you want to die, kill yourself.
I can't.
I kill myself.
And they'll start to doubt the information I gave them.
But if you were to kill me, they wouldn't bat an eye.
Hey, Mika.
If you don't hurry up, we'll leave you behind.
And bring that pathetic human.
Come on.
I think she told us everything she knows.
Not yet.
We can still get more information out of...
Look out!
You bastards!
I know your game.
You're eventually going to kill me anyway.
I'll be there, hold on.
Death trail through somehow.
Somewhere I am now.
Oh, man.
You killed her before we got to play.
Who cares about what the livestock has to say?
Well, you've got a point there.
The blind loyalty these humans have is a little frightening.
The Japanese Imperial Demon Army may prove to be more of a problem than we expected.
True, these humans are nothing alone.
But when they gang up, they're kind of dangerous.
Let's head to the Botanical Garden.
We can't allow the 17th Progenitor to be killed as well.
I'm gonna take a different route.
This human may have been scared for her life, but we can take her word alone.
Let me borrow five soldiers and I'll go see what's happening at City Hall, just in case.
That's not a bad idea.
We'll regroup when you're done.
That story protected you.
Maybe you were his comrade.
No.
You probably just used him like all the others do.
Okay, follow me.
Let's see what's going on at City Hall.
I'm coming, old friend.
Is there something wrong?
Uh, no.
It's just getting really cloudy.
It's the perfect weather to launch an attack.
Yeah.
Let's get on with it.
I'm coming.
Next time on Seraph of the End, Shinya and Gurin.